Washington Area Performing Arts Video Archives (WAPAVA)
DC Public Library Special Collections
Washington Area Performing Arts Video Archives (WAPAVA) Collection
1993-2016
DC Public Library, Special Collections
0.0 linear feet; 00 boxes
047
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Series 1
  - Escape from Happiness - Round House Theatre, 1995-03-22 - 1995-04-16 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - First Lady Suite - Signature Theatre, 1995-03-15 - 1995-04-15 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Happy Days - Scena Theatre, 1900-01-00 - 1900-01-00 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - I Could Stop on a Dime and Get Ten Cents Change - Theatre of the First Amendment, George, 1995-03-22 - 1995-04-09 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Shadowlands - Olney Theatre, 1993-08-10 - 1993-09-05 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Catskills Tzimmis - Theater J, 1995-04-26 - 1995-05-27 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Food Chain, The - Wolly Mammoth, 1994-06-16 - 1994-07-17 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Jacques Brel is Alive and Well and Living in Paris - Olney Theatre, 1995-06-13 - 1995-07-16 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Merchant of Venice - Folger Theatre, 1995-06-03 - 1995-06-25 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Rhinoceros - Studio Theatre, 1995-03-08 - 1995-04-09 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Three Sisters, The - Studio Theatre, 1995-01-08 - 1995-12-10 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - View from the Bridge, A - Source Theatre, 1995-11-15 - 1995-12-10 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Broken Glass - Olney Theatre, 1996-03-19 - 1996-04-21 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Dangerous Border Game - Dance Place, 1996-03-29 - 1996-03-31 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Macbeth - Shakespeare Theatre, 1995-09-12 - 1995-11-04 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Tale of the Wolf - Washington Stage Guild, 1995-10-25 - 1995-11-26 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Torn from the Headlines - Everyday Theatre, 1996-01-27 - 1996-02-18 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Wanted - Woolly Mammoth Theatre, 1995-06-12 - 1995-07-09 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - All’s Well That Ends Well - Shakespeare Theatre, 1996-02-06 - 1996-03-24 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Candide - Arena Stage, 1996-03-27 - 1996-04-28 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Henry V - Shakespeare Theatre, 1995-11-28 - 1996-01-14 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Tappers with Attitude - Hartke Theatre, Catholic University, 1996-05-18 - 1999-05-18 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Wonderful One-Hoss Shay, The - Theatre of the First Amendment, George, 1996-03-20 - 1996-04-16 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - An Almost Holy Picture - Roundhouse Theatre, 1996-03-27 - 1996-04-28 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Crypotogram - Studio Theatre, 1996-02-16 - 1996-03-31 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Dance of Death - Arena Stage, 1996-02-16 - 1996-03-31 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Moving Forward: Perspectives in Asian Dance - National Portrait Gallery, 1996-05-20 - 1996-05-20 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Passion - Signature Theatre, 1996-04-24 - 1996-06-30 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Volpone - Shakespeare Theatre, 1996-04-16 - 1996-06-02 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Gigli Concert - Wolly Mammoth, 1996-06-03 - 1996-07-22 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Harlem Nutcracker - George Mason Center for the Arts, 1996-11-22 - 1996-11-24 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Measure for Measure - Shakespeare Theatre, 1996-05-05 - 1996-06-27 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Sisterhood - Roundhouse Theatre, 1996-05-29 - 1996-06-22 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Tall Tales, White Lies, Local Color and… - Kennedy Center, Terrace Theatre, 1995-02-16 - 1995-02-26 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Women and the - Le Neon Theatre, 1996-12-08 - 1996-12-08 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Cryptogram - Studio Theatre, 1996-11-12 - 1997-01-12 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - One Shoe Off - Round House Theatre, 1996-11-06 - 1996-12-08 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Pavlov 2 Segundos Antes del Crimen - Gala Teatro Hispanico, 1996-05-11 - 1996-06-04 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Sweet Revenge of Lousia May - Olney Theatre, 1994-09-27 - 1994-10-23 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Three Nights in Tehran - Signature Theatre, 1996-11-15 - 1996-12-22 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Cigarettes and Chocolate - The Potomac Theatre Project at Olney T, 1997-01-10 - 1997-02-02 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Closetland - The Potomac Theatre Project at Olney T, 1997-01-10 - 1997-02-02 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Murder in the Cathedral - The Washington Stage Guild, 1997-01-01 - 1997-02-02 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Never the Sinner - Rep Theatre, 1997-08-19 - 1997-09-28 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Sylvia - Studio Theatre, 1997-03-02 - 1997-04-20 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - UBU Cuckolded - Theatre du Jour and DCAC Productions, 1996-12-06 - 1997-01-08 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Chips - Washington’s Shakespeare Company, 1997-01-25 - 1997-02-25 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Moby Dick Rehearsed by Orson Wells - The American Century Theatre, 1997-05-01 - 1997-05-24 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Sunday in the Park with George - Arena Stage, 1997-04-12 - 1997-06-14 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Antony and Cleopatra - Shakespeare Theatre, 1996-12-13 - 1997-01-19 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Henry VI - Shakespeare Theatre, 1996-09-17 - 1996-11-03 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Things that Break - Theatre of the First Amendment, 1997-03-19 - 1997-04-16 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Harvey Milk Show - Source Theatre, 1997-05-06 - 1997-06-01 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Melville Slept Here - Signature Theatre, 1997-03-26 - 1997-05-04 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Mourning Becomes Electra - Shakespeare Theatre, 1997-04-29 - 1997-06-15 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Shehechianu - The Lansburgh/Liz Lerman Dance Excha, 1997-06-19 - 1997-06-22 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Brimstone and Treacle - Wooly Mammoth Theatre, 1997-10-27 - 1997-11-19 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Cherry Orchard, The - Source Theatre, 1998-03-14 - 1998-04-12 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - El Publico/The Public (in English and Spanish) - Theatro de La Lune, 1998-03-04 - 1998-04-19 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Fall of the House of Usher - DCAC, 1997-09-18 - 1997-10-25 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Look! We Have Come Through! - Olney Theatre, 1997-10-21 - 1997-11-23 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Salome - LeNeon Theatre, 1997-10-24 - 1997-11-23 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Tripping through the Car House and Post-Show… - Woolly Mammoth, 1997-03-24 - 1900-01-00 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - House Arrest - Arena Stage, 1997-11-07 - 1998-01-14 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Old Wicked Songs - The Studio Theatre, 1997-11-05 - 2029-12-21 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Romeo and Juliet - The Folger Shakespeare Theatre, 1997-11-14 - 1997-12-14 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Tempest, The - Shakespeare Theatre, 1997-09-02 - 1997-10-26 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Anna Karenina, Act I and II - Washington Stage Guild, 1997-12-31 - 1998-02-01 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Fixx, The - Signature Theatre, 1998-03-17 - 1998-05-29 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Jack and Jill - Round House Theatre, 1998-01-07 - 1998-02-01 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Kudzu: A Southern Musical - Ford’s Theatre, 1998-03-04 - 1998-06-23 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Peter Pan - Olney Theatre, 1997-12-02 - 1998-01-14 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Playing Juliet Casting Othello - The Folger Shakespeare Theatre, 1998-01-09 - 1998-02-01 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Blues Rooms - Theatre of the First Amendment, 1998-03-18 - 1998-04-05 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Chaos Standing - DCAC at Gala Hispanic, 1998-04-10 - 1998-04-11 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Hip Hop Nightmares of Jujube Brown - African Continuum Theatre Company, 1998-03-05 - 1998-03-22 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Jujube Brown - African Continuum Theatre Company, 1998-03-06 - 1998-03-22 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Lovers and Executioners - Arena Stage, 1998-02-27 - 1998-04-05 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Marat/Sade - Washington Shakespeare Company, 1998-03-12 - 1998-04-19 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Dead Funny - Wolly Mammoth, 1993-06-03 - 1998-07-12 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Great Expectations: The Musical - Interact Theatre Company, 1998-08-05 - 1998-09-20 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Merry Wives of Windsor, The - The Shakespeare Theatre, 1998-03-24 - 1998-05-10 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Nijinsky’s Last Dance - Signature Theatre, 1998-11-02 - 1998-12-13 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Peer Gynt - Washington Shakespeare Company, 1998-01-20 - 1998-03-08 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Pericles - Washington Shakespeare Company, 1998-05-19 - 1998-06-27 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - State of the Union - Ford’s Theatre, 1998-04-01 - 1998-05-03 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Steward of Christendom, The - The Studio Theatre, 1998-04-01 - 1998-05-03 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Camille - Olney Theatre, 1998-08-11 - 1998-09-20 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Field - The Keegan Theatre, 1998-08-21 - 1998-09-05 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Love Songs - WPAS, Anacostia Museum, Dance place, 1998-10-16 - 1998-10-17 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Rules of the Game, The - The Washington Stage Guild, 1998-04-22 - 1998-05-24 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Waiting for Godot - Studio Theatre, 1998-09-02 - 1998-10-25 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Women of No Importance, A - Shakespeare Theatre, 1998-09-01 - 1998-10-17 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Dangerous Liaisons - Source Theatre Company, 1998-08-19 - 1998-10-01 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Metamorphosis Washington - Shakespeare Company, 1998-10-08 - 1998-11-15 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Molly Smith with Paula Vogel - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1998-10-15 - 1998-10-15 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Nightingale, The - The Kennedy Center/Imagination Celebr, 1999-01-27 - 1999-01-27 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Ride Across Lake Constance, The - DCAC/Fraudulent Productions, 1998-09-18 - 1998-10-24 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Lion in Winter - Round House Theatre, 1998-11-11 - 1998-12-12 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Michael Kahn with Alfred Uhry - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1999-03-17 - 1999-03-17 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Michael Kahn with Edward Albee - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1999-03-13 - 1999-03-13 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Michael Kahn with Eric Bogosian - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1999-02-17 - 1999-02-17 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Michael Kahn with Wendy Wasserstein… - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1999-03-10 - 1999-03-10 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - As You Like It - Folger Theatre, 1997-02-11 - 1997-04-06 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Much Ado About Nothing - Folger Elizabetha Theatre, 1998-11-14 - 1998-12-20 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - All’s Well That Ends Well at the Carter Barron - Shakespeare Theatre, 1998-06-06 - 1998-06-21 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Othello - Shakespeare Theatre, 1997-11-11 - 1998-01-04 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Sweet Bird of Youth - Shakespeare Theatre, 1998-05-26 - 1998-07-19 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Little Tragedies - Stanislavsky Theater Studio, 1998-12-04 - 1999-01-10 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Taming of the Shrew - Washington Shakespeare Company, 1999-04-08 - 1999-05-23 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Twelfth Night - Shakespeare Theatre, 1998-11-03 - 1999-01-02 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Chinese Art of Placement - Wolly Mammoth Theatre, 1999-06-07 - 1999-07-18 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Christmas at the Old Bull and Bush - Interact Theatre Co., 1998-11-27 - 1999-01-10 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Conspiring to Create the World of the Play: Behind the Scenes at the - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1999-02-08 - 1999-02-08 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - How I Learned to Drive - Arena Stage, 1999-04-23 - 1999-06-20 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - King John - The Shakespeare Theatre, 1999-08-31 - 2000-01-28 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Lucia Mad - The Washington Stage Guild, 1998-12-30 - 1999-02-14 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Beckett Festival - LeNeon Theatre, 1999-03-26 - 1999-05-02 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Molly’s Salon (with hot n. throbbin)/ Steven Samuel - Arena Stage, 1999-09-13 - 1999-09-13 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Molly’s Salon (with How I learned to Drive)/ Paula - Arena Stage, 1999-04-26 - 1999-04-26 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Oak and Ivy - Arena Stage, 1999-02-12 - 1999-04-04 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Animal Crackers - Arena Stage, 1999-03-26 - 1999-05-30 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Coriolanus - The Shakespeare Theatre, 2000-01-18 - 2000-03-12 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Hot’n’throbbing - Arena Stage, 1999-09-03 - 1999-10-17 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Merchant of Venice - Shakespeare Theatre, 1999-03-25 - 1999-07-18 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Communicating Doors - Round House Theater, 1993-11-03 - 1999-12-12 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Dresser - The Folger Shakespeare Library, 1999-04-03 - 1999-05-03 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Molly Smith (w/ Blue)/Charles Randolph-Wright - Arena Stage, 2000-04-17 - 2000-04-17 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Revenger’s Tragedy - Shakespeare Company, 2000-01-27 - 2000-03-05 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Sins of Sor Juana - Theater of the First Amendment, George, 1999-11-01 - 1999-11-30 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - El Saludador - Theatro de La Lune, 2000-05-05 - 2000-07-11 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Euripides’ HECUBA - African Continuum Theatre, 1998-11-02 - 1998-11-22 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Sueno’ - Olney Theatre (Potomac Theater Festival), 2000-07-11 - 2000-08-13 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Country Wife - The Shakespeare Theatre, 2000-03-28 - 2000-05-14 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Desk Set - Studio Theatre, 1999-05-05 - 1999-06-20 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Ins and Outs - Source Theatre, 1999-12-04 - 2000-01-02 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Nixon’s Nixon - Round House Theatre, 1999-12-04 - 2000-01-02 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Guys and Dolls - Arena, 1999-12-07 - 2000-02-20 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Idiot, The - Stanislavsky Theater Studio, 1999-11-14 - 1999-12-19 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Rhythm Club, The - Signature Theatre, 2000-09-05 - 2000-10-22 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Scared of Myself: The Return of Uncle Silvana - Washington Performing Arts Society, 2000-04-02 - 2000-04-02 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Trojan Women - The Shakespeare Theatre, 1999-03-22 - 1999-05-08 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Hughie - The Washington Stage Guild, 2000-02-12 - 2000-03-14 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Last Game Show, The - Horizons Theatre, 2000-03-01 - 2000-04-01 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Master Harold and the Boys - Studio Theatre, 2000-01-05 - 2000-02-13 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Mystery of Irma Vep - Rep Stage, 2000-02-03 - 2000-03-12 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Sing Down the Moon - Theater of the First Amendment, 2000-03-08 - 2000-04-21 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Where the Wild Things Are - Washington Ballet, 2000-03-09 - 2000-03-12 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - As You Like It - Washington Shakespeare Company, 2000-03-30 - 2000-05-07 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Available Light - Signature Theatre, 2000-03-07 - 2000-04-16 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Deborah Riley Dance Projects - Dance Place, 2000-04-15 - 2000-04-16 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Life in Refusal - Theater J, 2000-03-04 - 2000-04-02 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Michael Kahn with Lanford Wilson: Leading… - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 2000-03-08 - 2000-03-08 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Michael Kahn with Marsha Norman: Playwright’s… - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 2000-03-15 - 2000-03-15 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Michael Kahn with Peter Shaffer - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 2000-03-01 - 2000-03-01 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Michael Kahn with Tony Kushner: Playwrights… - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 2000-04-24 - 2000-04-24 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Tales of the Blue Crab - Discovery Theater and the Smithsonian, 2000-04-03 - 2000-04-19 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Blue - Arena Stage, 2000-04-15 - 2000-06-11 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Marisol - Trumpet Vine Theatre Company, 2000-04-06 - 2000-04-23 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Moliere: Le malade Imaginaire - Stanislavsky Theater Studio, 2000-04-19 - 2000-05-21 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Too True to be Good - Washington Stage Guild, 2000-03-23 - 2000-04-30 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Camino Real - Shakespeare Theater, 2000-05-30 - 2000-07-23 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Cyrano de Bergerac - LeNeon Theatre, 1999-11-29 - 1999-12-18 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Hamlet - Folger Shakespeare Library, 1999-10-30 - 1999-11-05 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - King Lear - Shakespeare Theatre, 1999-08-31 - 1999-10-24 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Men on the Verge of a his-panic breakdown - Round House Theatre, 2000-04-28 - 2000-05-15 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Midsummer Night’s Dream - Shakespeare Theatre, 1999-11-09 - 2000-01-02 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Dark Kalamazoo - Wolly Mammoth Theatre Company, 1999-11-08 - 1999-12-12 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Leaving the Summer Lands - Tribute Productions`, 2000-06-11 - 2000-07-01 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Mary and Myra - Contemporary American Theater Festival, 2000-07-07 - 2000-07-30 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Great White Hope, The - Arena, 2000-08-25 - 2000-10-15 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Hot House - Longacre Lea Productions, 2000-08-09 - 2000-08-27 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Riddle Me a Prince - BAPA’s Imagination Stage, 2000-06-11 - 2000-08-27 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Therese Raquin - Olney Theatre, 2000-08-22 - 2000-09-24 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Molly’s Salon (for the Great White Hope) - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 2000-08-28 - 2000-08-28 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - My Foot My Tutor - Fraudulent Productions, 2000-08-31 - 2000-10-07 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Timon of Athens - Shakespeare Theatre, 2000-08-29 - 2000-10-22 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Bird’s Nest: Echoes of the Jazz Age - The Washington Ballet, 2000-10-11 - 2000-10-15 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Closer - Source Theatre, 2000-09-06 - 2000-10-14 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Incident at Vichy - Washington Jewish Theatre and Washin, 2000-09-21 - 2000-09-24 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Lonesome West, The - Rep Stage, 2000-09-22 - 2000-10-15 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Vigil - Studio Theatre, 2000-09-06 - 2000-11-05 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Washington Ballet Jazz and Blues Performance - Washington Ballet, 2000-10-11 - 2000-10-15 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Buffalo Hair - African Continuum Theatre Company, 2000-12-05 - 2000-12-17 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - K2 - Arena Stage, 1999-12-08 - 2000-01-28 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Richard II - The Shakespeare Theatre, 2000-11-07 - 2000-12-31 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Tempest, The - Folger Theatre, 2000-11-28 - 2000-12-03 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Theatre and French Wit: A Double Bill - Le Neon Theatre, 2000-11-25 - 2000-12-17 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Apollo: To the Moon - Kennedy Center: Imagination Celebration, 2001-01-12 - 2001-01-14 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Chesapeake - Source Theatre, 2000-12-01 - 2001-01-20 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Faust - Stanislavsky Theatre Studio, 2000-12-01 - 2001-01-28 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - It’s New to Me: Choreographers Showcase - Arlington County Cultural Affairs Division, 2001-01-05 - 2001-01-05 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Stretch Marks - Charter Theatre, 2001-01-10 - 2001-01-28 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Coyote Builds North America - Arena Stage, 2001-03-02 - 2001-04-15 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Don Carlos - Shakespeare Theatre, 2001-01-16 - 2001-03-01 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Judas Kiss - Rep Stage, 2001-02-01 - 2001-02-18 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Love Labour’s Lost - Washington Shakespeare Company, 2001-02-08 - 2001-03-18 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Michael Kahn with Jane Alexander: Leading… - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 2001-02-21 - 2001-02-21 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Philadelphia Story, The - Rep Stage, 2000-11-02 - 2000-11-19 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - In the Garden - Signature Theatre, 2000-03-13 - 2000-04-29 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Love and Yearning in the Not-for-Profits and Other… - Theater J, 2001-03-04 - 2001-04-05 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Perseus Bayou - Theatre of the First Amendment, 2001-03-14 - 2001-04-01 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Romeo and Juliet Outreach Project - Shakespeare’s Sistah Theater Company, 2000-07-10 - 2000-07-10 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Science Quest! Inside the Double Helix - Discovery Theater: Smithsonian Associat, 2001-04-17 - 2001-05-04 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Crumbs from the Table of Joy - Round House Theater, 2001-03-14 - 2001-04-08 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Pageant - Rep Stage, 2001-03-16 - 2001-04-08 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Streetcar Named Desire, A - Arena Stage, 2001-03-30 - 2001-05-06 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Two Gentlemen of Verona - The Shakespeare Theater, 2001-03-27 - 2001-05-20 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Abducting Diana - Trumpet Vine Theater Company, 2001-05-03 - 2001-05-27 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - American Buffalo - Source Theatre, 2001-04-11 - 2001-05-19 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Invention of Love - Studio Theatre, 2001-03-28 - 2001-06-17 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Mystery School - Round House Theater, 2001-04-27 - 2001-05-13 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Illusion, The - Rorschach Theatre, 2001-06-05 - 2001-07-01 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Jitney - Studio Theater, 2001-05-16 - 2001-07-22 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Les Cloisons - LeNeon Theatre, 2001-05-24 - 2001-06-17 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Memory of Water, The - Washington Stage Guild, 2001-05-31 - 2001-07-08 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Paula Vogel/Wendy Wasserstein: Who Needs… - Arena Stage, 2001-06-01 - 2001-06-02 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Ride Down Mt. Morgan, The - Theater J, 2001-05-16 - 2001-06-17 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - As You Like It - Folger Theatre, 2001-05-13 - 2001-06-16 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Ferdinand the Bull - BAPA’s Imagination Station, 2001-06-16 - 2001-08-26 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Glengary Glen Ross - Keegan Theatre, 2001-07-13 - 2001-08-12 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Heaven - Woolly Mammoth Theatre Company, 2000-08-28 - 2000-10-08 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Hedda GAbler - Shakespeare Theatre, 2000-06-07 - 2000-07-29 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - In the Summer House - Washington Shakespeare Company, 2001-07-19 - 2001-08-19 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Agamemnon and His Daughters - Arena Stage, 2001-08-31 - 2001-10-07 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Grand Hotel - Signature Theatre, 2001-08-21 - 2001-10-07 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Italian American Reconciliation - Project Y Theatre Company, 2001-09-04 - 2001-10-10 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Oedipus Plays, The - Shakespeare Theatre, 2001-08-28 - 2001-10-21 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Prayer for Owen Meany, A - Round House Theatre, 2001-09-05 - 2001-10-07 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Problem Child - Round House Theatre, 2001-09-05 - 2001-10-07 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Da - Rep Stage, 2001-09-20 - 2001-10-07 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Macbeth - Folger Theatre, 2001-10-20 - 2001-12-02 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Michael Kahn’s 15th Anniversary: Artist and… - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 2001-10-03 - 2001-10-03 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Moon for the Misbegotten, A - Rep Stage, 2001-10-25 - 2001-11-18 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Hamlet - Shakespeare Theatre, 2001-11-06 - 2002-01-06 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Woyzeck - Catalyst Theatre Company, 2001-11-19 - 2001-12-23 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Angels in America Part One: Millennium Approaches (temp) - Signature Theatre, 1999-08-15 - 1999-08-15 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Angels in America Part Two: Perestroika (temp) - Signature Theatre, 1999-08-15 - 1999-08-15 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Death of a Salesman (temp) - Olney Theatre Center, 1999-10-24 - 1999-10-24 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Desdemona: A Play About a Handkerchief (temp) - The Theatre Conspiracy, 1999-05-28 - 1999-05-28 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Edmond (temp) - Source Theatre, 1999-09-26 - 1999-09-26 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Hoboken Station (temp) - Charter Theatre, 1999-04-22 - 1999-04-22 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Indian Ink (temp) - The Studio Theatre, 1999-10-17 - 1999-10-17 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Measure for Measure (temp) - Washington Shakespeare Company, 1999-10-23 - 1999-10-23 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Merry Wives of Windsor, The (temp) - The Shakespeare Theatre, 1999-06-10 - 1999-06-10 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Notebook of Trigorin, The (temp) - The Keegan Theater, 1999-11-13 - 1999-11-13 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Queen of Clubs (temp) - Signature Theatre, 1999-04-12 - 1999-04-12 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - R.U.R. (temp) - Fraudulent Productions, 1999-10-02 - 1999-10-02 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Sweeny Todd (temp) - Signature Theatre, 1999-11-07 - 1999-11-07 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Tomorrowland (temp) - Theater J, 1999-05-08 - 1999-05-08 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Translations (temp) - Rep Stage, 1999-10-07 - 1999-10-07 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - By Tooth or By Tongue - Source Theater Company, 2002-01-21 - 2002-02-20 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof - Keegan Theater, 2001-10-18 - 2001-11-18 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Learning Curves - Washington Shakespeare Company, 2002-01-21 - 2002-02-16 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Miklat - Theater J, 2002-01-07 - 2002-02-03 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Tiny Alice Washington - Shakespeare Company, 2002-01-11 - 2002-02-10 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Via Delarosa - Theatre J, 2002-01-12 - 2002-02-03 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Getting Married - The Washington Stage Guild, 2002-01-17 - 2002-02-24 (Box 51, Folder 1)